dailylife.com 2019-07-13

# Privacy Policy | Daily Life

### PRIVACY POLICY

#### Last Updated February 11, 2019

Thank you for visiting DailyLife.com (the “Website”). We provide this Privacy Policy to explain how DailyLife collects, uses and shares information from you when you use the Website and to help you make an informed decision as to whether to use or continue using the Website. 

#### 1.Who controls my personal information?

Any personal information provided to or gathered by DailyLife is controlled by:

New Peak Media INC.  
#220, 2181 Premier Way.   
Sherwood Park, Alberta   
T8H 2V1  
Canada.

#### 2\. What information does DailyLife collect from me?

The amount and type of information we gather depends upon your use of the Website and, in some cases, what type of information you choose to disclose. We may collect the following information from you:

**Personal Information**

We collect information from you when you voluntarily register with DailyLife and/or submit your personal information to us over the Website. Such personal information may include your name, email and postal addresses, phone number, birthdate, gender, and other information which you voluntarily provide to us. For example, if you order a report from us, we ask you to provide personal details about your birth in order to prepare the report. 

**Device/Internet Connection Information**

When you use the Website, we automatically gather information made available by your web browser (such as Microsoft Edge or Google Chrome), Internet service provider (such as Comcast or Time Warner), and device (such as your computer, phone, or tablet), depending on your settings for each. For example, we may collect your IP address, information about the operating system or type of device you use, the date and time you access the Website, and the location of your device.

**Information Provided by Third Parties**

DailyLife may receive information about you and your Internet activities if you have provided it to a Third-Party and we subsequently purchase, license, or otherwise acquire the information from the Third-Party. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your personal and online interests, and Internet browsing habits. These Third Parties may have collected such information by placing Cookies on your device, using web beacons, gathering IP addresses and log data, and so forth as described below. 

**Payment Information**

All payments are processed by third-party vendors, and not DailyLife itself. If you make a purchase on the Website, we will collect credit card numbers and related information, such as billing address, card number, and the expiration date of the card (“Credit Card Information”), but such information is sent directly to our payment processors using PCI Compliant rules/software and is never stored or otherwise retained by DailyLife. 

**Other Information**

From time to time, we may obtain other information from you, such as when you make a claim for a prize pursuant to a contest or other promotion run on the Website, when you request assistance through from our customer service department, and when you voluntarily subscribe to a DailyLife service or newsletter. You will always be asked to provide such other information voluntarily, and we will not collect it without your permission.

#### 3.How Does DailyLife Use Cookies?

**“Cookies”** are files that are placed on your computer or other device by websites you visit. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify you as a unique user of the Website. Cookies serve a lot of purposes and, among other things, help to customize your Internet experience, keep you logged into websites, remember your search terms, and advertise products or services to you. Some Cookies include tracking technology, such as web beacons, that can be used to track online behavioral habits for measurement and marketing purposes.

DailyLife currently uses Cookies and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information we already have in our database, for the following purposes:

  * **To Verify You.** We use Cookies to verify your account and make it so you do not have to reenter your login information each time you use the Website. 
  * **To Analyze User Trends.** We also use Cookies for analytics and performance—that is, to gather information that helps us understand how you and other users engage with the Website and our Third-Party partners and figure out how to do it better. 
  * **To Advertise to You.** We also use Cookies and web beacons, including those placed by Third Parties such as Google and Facebook, to deliver Personalized Ads that may be of interest to you. We may also use a web beacon in email messages sent to track your response. Cookies and web beacons also help us and our Third-Party advertising partners ensure you do not see the same advertisements over and over and to identify block unwanted ads. 

Like many websites, DailyLife uses Google services and Cookies to improve the Website, keep certain content free, and advertise to users like you, as described more fully below. As such, when you use the Website, your personal information may be shared with Google, and shared by Google with DailyLife. You can learn more about how Google uses Cookies, and how to manage your Cookie preferences in your Internet browser and revoke your consent to Personalized Ads, by visiting the[ Google Cookie Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en)

DailyLife also uses the Facebook cookie to deliver Personalized Ads to you, as that term is described below. You can learn more about how Facebook gathers and uses personal information via Cookies, including how to set your Cookie preferences within Facebook, by visiting the [Facebook Cookie Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy/cookies/)

Remember, you can change your Cookie settings in your Internet browser (e.g., Chrome, Edge, Firefox). For more information, see [www.CookieChoices.org. ](https://www.cookiechoices.org/)

#### 4\. How does DailyLife use my information?

We use the information we’ve gathered from you, including through Cookies and web beacons, for the following purposes:

**To Communicate with You**

We use information gathered on the Website to personalize communication with you, and to respond to your requests for products, services, and information. You can unsubscribe to advertising emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link within the email, or by contacting us as [support@DailyLife.com](mailto:support@DailyLife.com). Please note that, even if you unsubscribe from advertising emails, we will still send you any necessary, non-promotional emails about your account or updates to our privacy policy and terms.

**To Improve the Website**

DailyLife uses the information we collect from you and other users to provide and improve the Website. As explained above, we use Cookies, including those placed by Third Parties, to gather statistical information that helps us understand how you and other users engage with the Website and improve its performance.

**To Personalize Your User Experience**

We use information gathered from Cookies to determine whether you are logged in or not, and to allow you to set personal preferences when using the Website.

**To Advertise to You**

We use information gathered through Cookies and web beacons, including those placed by Third Parties, to deliver ads to you via the Website, and after you’ve left the Website, including advertising specific to your personal interests. The purpose of this practice, which is sometimes called “ **Personalized Ads** ,” “retargeting,” or “remarketing” is to deliver content and advertising that is of interest to you, and to avoid displaying irrelevant advertising to you. For example, if you look at a particular shirt for sale online, you may later see that same shirt advertised to you on Facebook and then again on DailyLife. 

**You can better learn about such Third-Party data collection and advertising practices, including how to revoke your consent to Personalized Ads, at the following websites:**

Our advertising endeavors help pay for the substantial free content on the Website, including daily blog articles. In addition, we may use personal information, such as your email address, to advertise and market our products and services by through email to you.

#### 5\. How does DailyLife share my information?

**To Fulfill Your Orders**

We may transfer your information to Third Parties when necessary to provide a product or service that you order from us. For example, as explained above, we will transfer your credit card information to our processor so that you can be charged (and we can be paid) for your purchase.

**To Advertise to Others**

We may share your reviews and comments about DailyLife to advertise and market our products and services. If you want us to stop using the personal data you have provided in these ways, please contact us at [privacy@DailyLife.com.](mailto:privacy@DailyLife.com)

**To Our Affiliated Companies**

We may disclose, transfer, and sell your information to our affiliated entities—that is, businesses that have common ownership with us—at our discretion, in which event, your information shall be treated by the affiliated entities in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Should DailyLife be subject to an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of control or business entity status, we reserve the right to transfer or assign your information as part of that acquisition, merger or sale.

**To Our Third-Party Partners**

We may disclose your personal information as needed to our Third-Party service providers and advertising partners. For example, we may share your email address with our email fulfillment provider. However, we will never sell your personal or non-personal data to any Third-Party. 

**To Comply with Legal Process and Prevent Harm**

We may disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes. In rare circumstances, we may disclose personal information when we believe it is necessary in order to prevent illegal, fraudulent, or injurious actions that may cause harm to individuals.

#### 6.How and Where Does DailyLife Secure My Information?

We use Third-Party vendors to store your information. These Third-Party vendors employ security measures (such as software and applications to block DDoS attacks, bots, malicious traffic, and internal firewalls) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**DailyLife stores personal information in the United States and Canada.** If you are visiting DailyLife.com from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States, and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using DailyLife.com you authorize and specifically consent to the transfer of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us.

#### 7\. How Can I Access or Correct My Information?

**You may access all information we’ve collected about you for purposes of correcting, amending, or deleting such information.** Access can be obtained by contacting [privacy@DailyLife.com](mailto:privacy@DailyLife.com). To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information to the Website may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at [privacy@DailyLife.com](mailto:privacy@DailyLife.com).

#### 8\. How does DailyLife protect the privacy of children?

DailyLife will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. We have designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

#### 9\. Does Daily Life respond to Do Not Track (DNT) Signals?

DNT is a feature offered by some browsers which, when enabled, sends a signal to websites to request that your browsing is not tracked. DailyLife does not currently respond to DNT requests.

#### 10\. What About Third-Party Practices?

**Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons**

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, Third Parties) who place advertisements on the Website and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. These practices are described more fully above in Sections 3 and 5. Except as expressly provided herein, we do not control Third Parties’ use of such technology and we have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. It is up to you to familiarize yourself with the privacy practices of such Third Parties.

**Third-Party Links**

The Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of Third Parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. We do not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third-Party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

#### 11\. How will I find out about changes to the Privacy Policy?

Each time you use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Although most changes are likely to be minor, we reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy by posting such modification on this page; however, if changes are significant, we may provide a more prominent notice or email you. Unless we receive your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier version.
